{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Window Blind \u0026 Shade Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40166/":{"taskOID":40166,"originalTaskOID":40166,"setID":476,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500701,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the blinds or shades for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the blinds or shades for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1084,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms in Need of Blinds/Shades","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In which rooms would you like to install blinds or shades? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1089,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Blind/Shade","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which type of blinds would you like to have installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4734,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Pleated shade","answerDisplayText":"Pleated shade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1307,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cellular shade - double cell","answerDisplayText":"Cellular shade - double cell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7058,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood blinds","answerDisplayText":"Wood blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7133,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Woven wood shades (not available w/remote)","answerDisplayText":"Woven wood shades (not available w/remote)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2361,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fabric shades/Roman shades","answerDisplayText":"Fabric shades/Roman shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5385,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Roller shades (not available w/remote)","answerDisplayText":"Roller shades (not available w/remote)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3818,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Metal horizontal blinds:  5/8, 1 or 2\" widths","answerDisplayText":"Metal horizontal blinds:  5/8, 1 or 2\" widths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6708,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vinyl horizontal blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl horizontal blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6678,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2401,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Faux wood blinds","answerDisplayText":"Faux wood blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1090,"questionDisplayText":"Special features requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special features you want to have installed.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Top down/ bottom up (for shades)","answerDisplayText":"Top down/ bottom up (for shades)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5146,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","answerDisplayText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2308,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extension brackets","answerDisplayText":"Extension brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":370,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"2 blinds on one headrail","answerDisplayText":"2 blinds on one headrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6653,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5418,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Room darkening","answerDisplayText":"Room darkening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4917,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Privacy/Sheer","answerDisplayText":"Privacy/Sheer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500701,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the blinds or shades for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the blinds or shades for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1084,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms in Need of Blinds/Shades","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In which rooms would you like to install blinds or shades? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3052,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1089,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Blind/Shade","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which type of blinds would you like to have installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4734,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Pleated shade","answerDisplayText":"Pleated shade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1307,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cellular shade - double cell","answerDisplayText":"Cellular shade - double cell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7058,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood blinds","answerDisplayText":"Wood blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7133,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Woven wood shades (not available w/remote)","answerDisplayText":"Woven wood shades (not available w/remote)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2361,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fabric shades/Roman shades","answerDisplayText":"Fabric shades/Roman shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5385,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Roller shades (not available w/remote)","answerDisplayText":"Roller shades (not available w/remote)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3818,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Metal horizontal blinds:  5/8, 1 or 2\" widths","answerDisplayText":"Metal horizontal blinds:  5/8, 1 or 2\" widths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6708,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vinyl horizontal blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl horizontal blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6678,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2401,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Faux wood blinds","answerDisplayText":"Faux wood blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4734,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Pleated shade","answerDisplayText":"Pleated shade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1307,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cellular shade - double cell","answerDisplayText":"Cellular shade - double cell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7058,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood blinds","answerDisplayText":"Wood blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7133,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Woven wood shades (not available w/remote)","answerDisplayText":"Woven wood shades (not available w/remote)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2361,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fabric shades/Roman shades","answerDisplayText":"Fabric shades/Roman shades","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5385,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Roller shades (not available w/remote)","answerDisplayText":"Roller shades (not available w/remote)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3818,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Metal horizontal blinds:  5/8, 1 or 2\" widths","answerDisplayText":"Metal horizontal blinds:  5/8, 1 or 2\" widths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6708,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Vinyl horizontal blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl horizontal blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6678,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Vertical blinds","answerDisplayText":"Vertical blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2401,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Faux wood blinds","answerDisplayText":"Faux wood blinds","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8117,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1090,"questionDisplayText":"Special features requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special features you want to have installed.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Top down/ bottom up (for shades)","answerDisplayText":"Top down/ bottom up (for shades)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5146,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","answerDisplayText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2308,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extension brackets","answerDisplayText":"Extension brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":370,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"2 blinds on one headrail","answerDisplayText":"2 blinds on one headrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6653,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5418,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Room darkening","answerDisplayText":"Room darkening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4917,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Privacy/Sheer","answerDisplayText":"Privacy/Sheer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Top down/ bottom up (for shades)","answerDisplayText":"Top down/ bottom up (for shades)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5146,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","answerDisplayText":"Remote control/optional wall mounted electric eye","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2308,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Extension brackets","answerDisplayText":"Extension brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":370,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"2 blinds on one headrail","answerDisplayText":"2 blinds on one headrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6653,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","answerDisplayText":"Valance (vertical blinds)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5418,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Room darkening","answerDisplayText":"Room darkening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4917,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Privacy/Sheer","answerDisplayText":"Privacy/Sheer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"__cache./api/resource/task/40166/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40166,"taskName":"Blinds or Shades - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Blinds or Shades","xmTaskDescriptor":"Window Blind \u0026 Shade Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":275,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Blinds drapery binds mini repalce","textMessagingName":"Install Blinds","rolloverLongDesc":"Mostly handled by specialty firms that install what they sell. Usually only a handyman service will install window treatments the consumer has purchased on their own.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes minis, verticals, Venetian, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Blinds or Shades.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Blind Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Window Shades \u0026 Blinds","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":24,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, you might consider ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"requesting a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Blinds or Shades Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Blinds or Shades - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Blind and Shade Project","urlName":"Blinds-or-Shades-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Blind Installation Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"blinds, window coverings, windows, coverings, shades,  mini blinds, mini-blinds, window treaments","emcCategoryOid":-12079,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":476,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}